Guide to the Harlequin Romance Collection of Treva M. Taylor 1967-1996 (Bulk 1974-1996) MSS.216
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Harlequin Romance Novels
  - Harlequin Romance 2276. Way, Margaret: White Magnolia. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2277. Wibberley, Mary: The Dark Warrior. (Harlequin Books), 1979 (Box 20, Folder 469)
  - Harlequin Romance 2278. Bevan, Gloria: Kowhai Country. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2279. Peake, Lilian: Stranger on the Beach. (Harlequin Books), 1979 (Box 20, Folder 470)
  - Harlequin Romance 2280. Mayo, Margaret: Afraid to Love. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2281. Summers, Essie: My Lady of the Fuchsias. (Harlequin Books), 1979 (Box 21, Folder 471)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042233455
  - Harlequin Romance 2282. Lewty, Marjorie: A Very Special Man. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2283. Allyne, Kerry: The Plains of Promise. (Harlequin Books), 1979 (Box 21, Folder 472)
  - Harlequin Romance 2284. Pargeter, Margaret: Only You. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2285. Corrie, Jane: Caribbean Cocktail. (Harlequin Books), 1979 (Box 21, Folder 473)
  - Harlequin Romance 2286. May, Wynne: A Scarf of Flame. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2287. MacLean, Jan: Bitter Homecoming. (Harlequin Books), 1979 (Box 21, Folder 474)
  - Harlequin Romance 2288. Cork, Dorothy: Walkabout Wife. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2289. Steele, Jessica: Spring Girl. (Harlequin Books), 1979 (Box 21, Folder 475)
  - Harlequin Romance 2290. Burchell, Mary: Bargain Wife. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2291. Way, Margaret: Valley of the Moon. (Harlequin Books), 1979 (Box 21, Folder 476)
  - Harlequin Romance 2292. Clair, Daphne: The Sleeping Fire. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2293. Donnelly, Jane: A Savage Sanctuary. (Harlequin Books), 1979 (Box 21, Folder 477)
  - Harlequin Romance 2294. Gray, Janice: Heart of the Scorpion. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2295. MacLean, Jan: Early Summer. (Harlequin Books), 1979 (Box 21, Folder 478)
  - Harlequin Romance 2296. Pargeter, Margaret: The Devil's Bride. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2297. Steele, Jessica: The Icicle Heart. (Harlequin Books), 1979 (Box 21, Folder 479)
  - Harlequin Romance 2298. Wibberley, Mary: Runaway Marriage. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2299. Arbor, Jane: Pact without Desire. (Harlequin Books), 1979 (Box 21, Folder 480)
  - Harlequin Romance 2300. Ashton, Elizabeth: Moonlight on the Nile. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2301. Neels, Betty: The Promise of Happiness. (Harlequin Books), 1979 (Box 21, Folder 481)
  - Harlequin Romance 2302. Steele, Jessica: Hostile Engagement. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2303. Stratton, Rebecca: Close to the Heart. (Harlequin Books), 1979 (Box 21, Folder 482)
  - Harlequin Romance 2304. Whittal, Yvonne: Bitter Enchantment. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2305. Britt, Katrina: The Man on the Peak. (Harlequin Books), 1979 (Box 21, Folder 483)
  - Harlequin Romance 2306. Dawson, Elizabeth: The Bending Reed. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2307. Firth, Suzanna: Dark Encounter. (Harlequin Books), 1979 (Box 21, Folder 484)
  - Harlequin Romance 2308. Gilbert, Jacqueline: Scorpio Summer. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2309. Steele, Jessica: Pride's Master. (Harlequin Books), 1980 (Box 21, Folder 485)
  - Harlequin Romance 2310. Wentworth, Sally: The Ice Maiden. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2311. Ashton, Elizabeth: The Joyous Adventure. (Harlequin Books), 1980 (Box 21, Folder 486)
  - Harlequin Romance 2312. Carter, Rosemary: Return to Devil's View. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2313. Corrie, Jane: The Spanish Uncle. (Harlequin Books), 1980 (Box 21, Folder 487)
  - Harlequin Romance 2314. Neels, Betty: Midnight Sun's Magic. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2315. Pollock, Rosemary: White Hibiscus. (Harlequin Books), 1980 (Box 21, Folder 488)
  - Harlequin Romance 2316. Wibberley, Mary: With This Ring. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2317. Carson, Angela: The Vital Spark. (Harlequin Books), 1980 (Box 21, Folder 489)
  - Harlequin Romance 2318. Dingwell, Joyce: The Angry Man. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2319. Gillen, Lucy: Hepburn's Quay. (Harlequin Books), 1980 (Box 21, Folder 490)
  - Harlequin Romance 2320. Graham, Elizabeth: Devil on Horseback. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2321. May, Wynne: Island of Cyclones. (Harlequin Books), 1980 (Box 21, Folder 491)
  - Harlequin Romance 2322. Summers, Essie: One More River to Cross. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2323. Allyne, Kerry: Across the Great Divide. (Harlequin Books), 1980 (Box 21, Folder 492)
  - Harlequin Romance 2324. Ashton, Elizabeth: Reluctant Partnership. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2325. Donnelly, Jane: A Man to Watch. (Harlequin Books), 1980 (Box 22, Folder 493)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042233463
  - Harlequin Romance 2326. Graham, Elizabeth: Come Next Spring. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2327. Mayo, Margaret: Stormy Affair. (Harlequin Books), 1980 (Box 22, Folder 494)
  - Harlequin Romance 2328. Way, Margaret: Blue Lotus. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2329. Clair, Daphne: The Jasmine Bride. (Harlequin Books), 1980 (Box 22, Folder 495)
  - Harlequin Romance 2330. Ellis, Janine: Rough Justice. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2331. Lewty, Marjorie: A Certain Smile. (Harlequin Books), 1980 (Box 22, Folder 496)
  - Harlequin Romance 2332. Rome, Margaret: Champagne Spring. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2333. Strutt, Sheila: The Master of Craighill. (Harlequin Books), 1980 (Box 22, Folder 497)
  - Harlequin Romance 2334. Van Der Zee, Karen: Sweet Not Always. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2335. Corrie, Jane: Tasmanian Tangle. (Harlequin Books), 1980 (Box 22, Folder 498)
  - Harlequin Romance 2336. Douglas, Sheila: Return to Lanmore. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2337. Harrel, Linda: Sea Lightning. (Harlequin Books), 1980 (Box 22, Folder 499)
  - Harlequin Romance 2338. Neels, Betty: Winter Wedding. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2339. Stratton, Rebecca: The Tears of Venus. (Harlequin Books), 1980 (Box 22, Folder 500)
  - Harlequin Romance 2340. Wibberley, Mary: A Dangerous Man. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2341. Allyne, Kerry: Sweet Harvest. (Harlequin Books), 1980 (Box 22, Folder 501)
  - Harlequin Romance 2342. Arbor, Jane: The Devil Drives. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2343. Britt, Katrina: Flowers for My Love. (Harlequin Books), 1980 (Box 22, Folder 502)
  - Harlequin Romance 2344. Firth, Susanna: Prince of Darkness. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2345. Reid, Henrietta: Paradise Plantation. (Harlequin Books), 1980 (Box 22, Folder 503)
  - Harlequin Romance 2346. Way, Margaret: The Butterfly and the Baron. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2347. Ashton, Elizabeth: The Rekindled Flame. (Harlequin Books), 1980 (Box 22, Folder 504)
  - Harlequin Romance 2348. MacLean, Jan: White Fire. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2349. Moore, Mary: Man of the High Country. (Harlequin Books), 1980 (Box 22, Folder 505)
  - Harlequin Romance 2350. Pargeter, Margaret: Autumn Spring. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2351. Peters, Sue: Shadow of an Eagle. (Harlequin Books), 1980 (Box 22, Folder 506)
  - Harlequin Romance 2352. Steele, Jessica: Hostage to Dishonour. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2353. Hampson, Anne: Temple of the Dawn. (Harlequin Books), 1980 (Box 22, Folder 507)
  - Harlequin Romance 2354. Stanford, Sondra: Bellefleur. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2355. Steele, Jessica: Turbulent Covenant. (Harlequin Books), 1980 (Box 22, Folder 508)
  - Harlequin Romance 2356. Stratton, Rebecca: Apollo's Daughter. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2357. Way, Margaret: The Golden Puma. (Harlequin Books), 1980 (Box 22, Folder 509)
  - Harlequin Romance 2358. Whittal, Yvonne: The Man from Amazibu Bay. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2359. Burchell, Mary: Nightingales. (Harlequin Books), 1980 (Box 22, Folder 510)
  - Harlequin Romance 2360. Mayo, Margaret: Valley of the Hawk. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2361. Wentworth, Sally: Garden of Thorns. (Harlequin Books), 1980 (Box 22, Folder 511)
  - Harlequin Romance 2362. Weston, Sophie: An Undefended City. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2363. Westwood, Gwen: Forgotten Bride. (Harlequin Books), 1980 (Box 22, Folder 512)
  - Harlequin Romance 2364. Wibberley, Mary: Dangerous Marriage. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2365. Corrie, Jane: The Station Boss. (Harlequin Books), 1980 (Box 22, Folder 513)
  - Harlequin Romance 2366. MacLeod, Jean S.: Brief Enchantment. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2367. Neels, Betty: Last April Affair. (Harlequin Books), 1980 (Box 22, Folder 514)
  - Harlequin Romance 2368. Peters, Sue: Claws of a Wildcat. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2369. Rome, Margaret: Marriage by Capture. (Harlequin Books), 1980 (Box 23, Folder 515)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042233471
  - Harlequin Romance 2370. Steele, Jessica: The Other Woman. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2371. Britt, Katrina: Island for Dreams. (Harlequin Books), 1980 (Box 23, Folder 516)
  - Harlequin Romance 2372. Cork, Dorothy: Outback Runaway. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2373. Donnelly, Jane: No Way Out. (Harlequin Books), 1980 (Box 23, Folder 517)
  - Harlequin Romance 2374. Graham, Elizabeth: Jacintha Point. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2375. Pargeter, Margaret: Kiss of a Tyrant. (Harlequin Books), 1980 (Box 23, Folder 518)
  - Harlequin Romance 2376. Stratton, Rebecca: Trader's Cay. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2377. Bevan, Gloria: Half a World Away. (Harlequin Books), 1981 (Box 23, Folder 519)
  - Harlequin Romance 2378. Bianchin, Helen: Master of Uluru. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2379. Burchell, Mary: Yours with Love. (Harlequin Books), 1981 (Box 23, Folder 520)
  - Harlequin Romance 2380. Carter, Rosemary: Man in the Shadows. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2381. Cowdray, Rosalind: Lord of Creation. (Harlequin Books), 1981 (Box 23, Folder 521)
  - Harlequin Romance 2382. Lewty, Marjorie: Prisoner of Paradise. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2383. Cooper, Ann: Fool's Paradise. (Harlequin Books), 1981 (Box 23, Folder 522)
  - Harlequin Romance 2384. Corrie, Jane: Island Fiesta. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2385. Mayo, Margaret: Burning Desire. (Harlequin Books), 1981 (Box 23, Folder 523)
  - Harlequin Romance 2386. Neels, Betty: The Silver Thaw. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2387. Way, Margaret: Lord of the High Valley. (Harlequin Books), 1981 (Box 23, Folder 524)
  - Harlequin Romance 2388. Wibberley, Mary: Man of Power. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2389. Allyne, Kerry: The Challenge. (Harlequin Books), 1981 (Box 23, Folder 525)
  - Harlequin Romance 2390. Cork, Dorothy: Barefoot Bride. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2391. Donald, Robyn: Bay of Stars. (Harlequin Books), 1981 (Box 23, Folder 526)
  - Harlequin Romance 2392. Douglas, Sheila: The Girl Between. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2393. Neels, Betty: Caroline's Waterloo. (Harlequin Books), 1981 (Box 23, Folder 527)
  - Harlequin Romance 2394. Steele, Jessica: The Magic of His Kiss. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2395. Ashton, Elizabeth: Borrowed Plumes. (Harlequin Books), 1981 (Box 23, Folder 528)
  - Harlequin Romance 2396. Arbor, Jane: Where the Wolf Leads. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2397. Britt, Katrina: The Wrong Man. (Harlequin Books), 1981 (Box 23, Folder 529)
  - Harlequin Romance 2398. Field, Sandra: The Winds of Winter. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2399. Stratton, Rebecca: The Inherited Bride. (Harlequin Books), 1981 (Box 23, Folder 530)
  - Harlequin Romance 2400. Way, Margaret: Flamingo Park. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2401. Ashton, Elizabeth: Sicilian Summer. (Harlequin Books), 1981 (Box 23, Folder 531)
  - Harlequin Romance 2402. Dingwell, Joyce: Come Back to Love. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2403. Neels, Betty: Hannah. (Harlequin Books), 1981 (Box 23, Folder 532)
  - Harlequin Romance 2404. Peake, Lilian: Promise at Midnight. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2405. Stratton, Rebecca: The Leo Man. (Harlequin Books), 1981 (Box 23, Folder 533)
  - Harlequin Romance 2406. Van Der Zee, Karen: Love Beyond Reason. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2407. Allyne, Kerry: Reunion at Pitereeka. (Harlequin Books), 1981 (Box 23, Folder 534)
  - Harlequin Romance 2408. Donnelly, Jane: When Lightning Strikes. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2409. Pargeter, Margaret: Dark Surrender. (Harlequin Books), 1981 (Box 23, Folder 535)
  - Harlequin Romance 2410. Peters, Sue: Marriage in Haste. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2411. Weale, Anne: The Last Night in Paradise. (Harlequin Books), 1981 (Box 23, Folder 536)
  - Harlequin Romance 2412. Whittal, Yvonne: Summer of the Weeping Rain. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2413. Corrie, Jane: Pirates' Lair. (Harlequin Books), 1981 (Box 24, Folder 537)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042233489
  - Harlequin Romance 2414. MacLeod, Jean S.: Black Sand, White Sand. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2415. Neels, Betty: When May Follows. (Harlequin Books), 1981 (Box 24, Folder 538)
  - Harlequin Romance 2416. Pargeter, Margaret: Deception. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2417. Westwood, Gwen: Zulu Moon. (Harlequin Books), 1981 (Box 24, Folder 539)
  - Harlequin Romance 2418. Wibberley, Mary: Fire and Steel. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2419. Arbor, Jane: One Brief Sweet Hour. (Harlequin Books), 1981 (Box 24, Folder 540)
  - Harlequin Romance 2420. Clair, Daphne: Never Count Tomorrow. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2421. Lewty, Marjorie: Love is a Dangerous Game. (Harlequin Books), 1981 (Box 24, Folder 541)
  - Harlequin Romance 2422. Pargeter, Margaret: Captivity. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2423. Peters, Sue: Tug of War. (Harlequin Books), 1981 (Box 24, Folder 542)
  - Harlequin Romance 2424. Steele, Jessica: Devil in Disguise. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2425. Ashton, Elizabeth: Silver Arrow. (Harlequin Books), 1981 (Box 24, Folder 543)
  - Harlequin Romance 2426. Bevan, Gloria: Master of Mahia. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2427. Gordon, Victoria: The Sugar Dragon. (Harlequin Books), 1981 (Box 24, Folder 544)
  - Harlequin Romance 2428. Rome, Margaret: The Wild Man. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2429. Way, Margaret: Temple of Fire. (Harlequin Books), 1981 (Box 24, Folder 545)
  - Harlequin Romance 2430. Whittal, Yvonne: Season of Shadows. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2431. Corrie, Jane: Bride for Sale. (Harlequin Books), 1981 (Box 24, Folder 546)
  - Harlequin Romance 2432. Dingwell, Joyce: The All-the-Way Man. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2433. Gordon, Victoria: Wolf at the Door. (Harlequin Books), 1981 (Box 24, Folder 547)
  - Harlequin Romance 2434. Stratton, Rebecca: The Silken Cage. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2435. Way, Margaret: Shadow Dance. (Harlequin Books), 1981 (Box 24, Folder 548)
  - Harlequin Romance 2436. Weale, Anne: Rain of Diamonds. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2437. Donald, Robyn: Iceberg. (Harlequin Books), 1981 (Box 24, Folder 549)
  - Harlequin Romance 2438. Gordon, Victoria: The Everywhere Man. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2439. Mayo, Margaret: A Taste of Paradise. (Harlequin Books), 1981 (Box 24, Folder 550)
  - Harlequin Romance 2440. Neels, Betty: Not Once But Twice. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2441. Whittal, Yvonne: The Light Within. (Harlequin Books), 1981 (Box 24, Folder 551)
  - Harlequin Romance 2442. Reid, Henrietta: Lord of the Isles. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2443. Armstrong, Lindsay: Spitfire. (Harlequin Books), 1981 (Box 24, Folder 552)
  - Harlequin Romance 2445. Rome, Margaret: Miss High and Mighty. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2446. Steele, Jessica: Innocent Abroad. (Harlequin Books), 1981 (Box 24, Folder 553)
  - Harlequin Romance 2447. Strutt, Sheila: On the Edge of Love. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2449. Britt, Katrina: Hotel Jacarandas. (Harlequin Books), 1981;1982 (Box 24, Folder 554)
  - Harlequin Romance 2450. Lewty, Marjorie: Beyond the Lagoon. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2451. Steele, Jessica: Bachelor's Wife. (Harlequin Books), 1982 (Box 24, Folder 555)
  - Harlequin Romance 2452. Stratton, Rebecca: The Black Invader. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2453. Summers, Essie: The Tender Leaves. (Harlequin Books), 1982 (Box 24, Folder 556)
  - Harlequin Romance 2454. Way, Margaret: The McIvor Affair. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2455. Bevan, Gloria: Emerald Cave. (Harlequin Books), 1982 (Box 24, Folder 557)
  - Harlequin Romance 2456. Donnelly, Jane: Flash Point. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2457. Field, Sandra: The Storms of Spring. (Harlequin Books), 1982 (Box 24, Folder 558)
  - Harlequin Romance 2458. Gordon, Victoria: Dream House. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2459. Harrel, Linda: Arctic Enemy. (Harlequin Books), 1982 (Box 25, Folder 559)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042233497
  - Harlequin Romance 2460. Lane, Roumelia: Dream Island. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2461. Daveson, Mons: Land of Tomorrow. (Harlequin Books), 1982 (Box 25, Folder 560)
  - Harlequin Romance 2462. Henaghan, Rosalie: Coppers Girl. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2463. Neels, Betty: An Apple from Eve. (Harlequin Books), 1982 (Box 25, Folder 561)
  - Harlequin Romance 2464. Rome, Margaret: Castle in Spain. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2465. Shaw, Catherine: Chateau of Dreams. (Harlequin Books), 1982 (Box 25, Folder 562)
  - Harlequin Romance 2466. Stratton, Rebecca: Dark Enigma. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2467. Arbor, Jane: Invisible Wife. (Harlequin Books), 1982 (Box 25, Folder 563)
  - Harlequin Romance 2468. Clifford, Kay: No Time for Love. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2469. Gordon, Victoria: Always the Boss. (Harlequin Books), 1982 (Box 25, Folder 564)
  - Harlequin Romance 2470. Murrey, Jeneth: The Bright Side of Dark. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2471. Peters, Sue: Dangerous Rapture. (Harlequin Books), 1982 (Box 25, Folder 565)
  - Harlequin Romance 2472. St. Clair, Joy: Heart Under Siege. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2473. Hilton, Margery: Way of a Man. (Harlequin Books), 1982 (Box 25, Folder 566)
  - Harlequin Romance 2474. Mayo, Margaret: Divided Loyalties. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2475. Pargeter, Margaret: At First Glance. (Harlequin Books), 1982 (Box 25, Folder 567)
  - Harlequin Romance 2476. Way, Margaret: North of Capricorn. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2477. Westwood, Gwen: Dangerous to Love. (Harlequin Books), 1982 (Box 25, Folder 568)
  - Harlequin Romance 2478. Whittal, Yvonne: The Spotted Plume. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2479. Allyne, Kerry: Mixed Feelings. (Harlequin Books), 1982 (Box 25, Folder 569)
  - Harlequin Romance 2480. Field, Sandra: Sight of a Stranger. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2481. Harvey, Samantha: The Driftwood Beach. (Harlequin Books), 1982 (Box 25, Folder 570)
  - Harlequin Romance 2482. MacLeod, Jean S.: Meeting in Madrid. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2483. Murrey, Jeneth: Hell is My Heaven. (Harlequin Books), 1982 (Box 25, Folder 571)
  - Harlequin Romance 2484. Weale, Anne: Bed of Roses. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2485. Lane, Roumelia: Desert Haven. (Harlequin Books), 1982 (Box 25, Folder 572)
  - Harlequin Romance 2486. Pollock, Rosemary: The Sun and Catriona. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2487. Rome, Margaret: King of Kielder. (Harlequin Books), 1982 (Box 25, Folder 573)
  - Harlequin Romance 2488. Stevens, Lynsey: Play Our Song Again. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2489. Stratton, Rebecca: The Golden Spaniard. (Harlequin Books), 1982 (Box 25, Folder 574)
  - Harlequin Romance 2490. Way, Margaret: Home to Morning Star. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2491. Dix, Isabel: Cast a Tender Shadow. (Harlequin Books), 1982 (Box 25, Folder 575)
  - Harlequin Romance 2492. Gilbert, Jacqueline: The Trodden Paths. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2493. Firth, Susanna: The Overlord. (Harlequin Books), 1982 (Box 25, Folder 576)
  - Harlequin Romance 2494. Steele, Jessica: But Know Not Why. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2495. Stevens, Lynsey: Race for Revenge. (Harlequin Books), 1982 (Box 25, Folder 577)
  - Harlequin Romance 2496. Strutt, Sheila: Stamp of Possession. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2499. MacLeod, Jean S.: Moreton's Kingdom. (Harlequin Books), 1982 (Box 25, Folder 578)
  - Harlequin Romance 2500. Neels, Betty: Judith. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2501. Peters, Sue: Man of Teak. (Harlequin Books), 1982 (Box 25, Folder 579)
  - Harlequin Romance 2502. Steele, Jessica: Dishonest Woman. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2503. Ashton, Elizabeth: White Witch. (Harlequin Books), 1982 (Box 26, Folder 580)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042233505
  - Harlequin Romance 2504. Ayre, Jessica: Not To Be Trusted. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2505. Clifford, Kay: A Temporary Affair. (Harlequin Books), 1982 (Box 26, Folder 581)
  - Harlequin Romance 2507. Stevens, Lynsey: Tropical Knight. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2508. Stratton, Rebecca: Charade. (Harlequin Books), 1982 (Box 26, Folder 582)
  - Harlequin Romance 2509. Arbor, Jane: The Price of Paradise. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2510. Donnelly, Jane: Diamond Cut Diamond. (Harlequin Books), 1982 (Box 26, Folder 583)
  - Harlequin Romance 2512. Moore, Mary: Run Before the Wind. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2513. Rome, Margaret: Valley of Gentians. (Harlequin Books), 1982 (Box 26, Folder 584)
  - Harlequin Romance 2514. Scott, Alexandra: This Side of Heaven. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2515. Allyne, Kerry: Valley of Lagoons. (Harlequin Books), 1982 (Box 26, Folder 585)
  - Harlequin Romance 2516. Clair, Daphne: Pacific Pretence. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2517. Cranmer, Kathryn: Passionate Enemies. (Harlequin Books), 1982 (Box 26, Folder 586)
  - Harlequin Romance 2518. Douglas, Sheila: The Uncertain Heart. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2519. Gair, Diana: Highlands Rapture. (Harlequin Books), 1982 (Box 26, Folder 587)
  - Harlequin Romance 2521. Corrie, Jane: Ross's Girl. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2522. Harvey, Samantha: The Distance Man. (Harlequin Books), 1982 (Box 26, Folder 588)
  - Harlequin Romance 2524. Reid, Henrietta: New Boss at Birchfields. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2525. Summers, Essie: Daughter of the Misty Gorges. (Harlequin Books), 1982 (Box 26, Folder 589)
  - Harlequin Romance 2526. West, Nicola: Devil's Gold. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2527. Allyne, Kerry: Spring Fever. (Harlequin Books), 1983 (Box 26, Folder 590)
  - Harlequin Romance 2528. Burchell, Mary: Masquerade with Music. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2529. Byfield, Sue: To Be or Not to Be. (Harlequin Books), 1983 (Box 26, Folder 591)
  - Harlequin Romance 2530. Gair, Diana: Jungle Antagonist. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2531. Gordon, Victoria: Dinner at Wyatt's. (Harlequin Books), 1983 (Box 26, Folder 592)
  - Harlequin Romance 2532. May, Wynne: Peacock in the Jungle. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2533. Clark, Sandra: Moonlight Enough. (Harlequin Books), 1983 (Box 26, Folder 593)
  - Harlequin Romance 2534. Daveson, Mons: My Lord Kasseem. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2535. George, Catherine: Reluctant Paragon. (Harlequin Books), 1983 (Box 26, Folder 594)
  - Harlequin Romance 2536. Lane, Roumelia: Lupin Valley. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2537. Way, Margaret: Spellbound. (Harlequin Books), 1983 (Box 26, Folder 595)